<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<!--
    ###################################################################################
    Antonov-Aircrafts and SpaceShuttle :: Herbert Wagner November2014-May2015
    Development is ongoing, see latest version: www.github.com/HerbyW
    This file is licenced under the terms of the GNU General Public Licence V3 or later
    
    Firefly: 3D model improvment
    Eagel: Liveries
    ###################################################################################
-->
<PropertyList>

  <title>Antonov AN-22A</title>
  <key>
    <name>s</name>
    <desc>Autostart</desc>
  </key>
  <key>
    <name>d</name>
    <desc>Open/Close left door</desc>
  </key>
  <key>
    <name>D</name>
    <desc>Open/Close right doors</desc>
  </key>
  <key>
    <name>E</name>
    <desc>Open/Close cargo doors</desc>
  </key>
  <key>
    <name>=</name>
    <desc>Parachutist</desc>
  </key>
  <key>
    <name>Delete</name>
    <desc>Reverser on/off</desc>
  </key>
  <key>
    <name>&lt;</name>
    <desc>Change Pilot Engineer View</desc>
  </key>
  <key>
    <name>y</name>
    <desc>Change Pilot Ramp View</desc>
  </key>
  <text>Welcome to Antonov-22A heavy cargo airplane by HerbyW
    
	Some instruments will show you metric values, some ft.
	
	Please refer to the AN-12 for more informations.
	
	There is a green panel in the middle console, the right switch makes the lights on.
	The middle switch is for nav-lights. The switch right from this panel is for landing and taxi lights.
	
	You have a panel with 5 lamps in the middle, the lower 3 are for trim-neutralisation.
		
	The Autopilot Helper panel in the top middle console is fully working.You may use some instruments to put in the values -
	- Heading Control: Heading Bug (HDG) and Course of ILS (NAV) are to set in the HSI (Horizontal Situation Indicator),
	- Velocity Control: Speed with Throttle are set in the Speed Indicator, then push IAS
	- Pitch/Attitude Control is working if you get the plane in a climbing or descending position and push the Button VS,
	- Wing leveler is activ when you push the AP button, it is also the AP activating Button,
	- APRP is used for intersepting the Glide Scope,
	- GPS for flying routes from the Route Manager,
	- ALT is holding your attidude, push again if the altidude will not get stable
	
	For ILS Landing you may use the little Instrument with the yellow and blue strips, the NAV Indicator, it
	gives you the indication that ILS and/or Glide Scope is intersepted.
	
	Flaps Controll Panel will give you the right level for landing (on the right side) and starting (on the left side),
	if the white strips are in the middle position (1-2 for starting, 2-4 for landing).
	
	Pushback car is now there. Do not use the brakes to stop backwards driving, use the pushback control please.
	
	Trails are now working only above 6000 ft, on ground it is not realistic.
	
	There are 2 Altimeters: one is in meter and mmHG, the other one in ft and inHG,
	 they are connected and you should set them to the ATIS information of the airport befor starting (not working for now).
	 
	The compasses are cleared of the magnetic variation.
	
	You may set your payloads and fuel in the menue.
	
	The payload menue gives you a 3rd weight for up to 3 Bradle Tanks, roll out with not more than 120 kts,
	activated in the Cabin Ramp Controll room with 2 switches: one for loading and unloading, one for jumping out,
	cargo door has to be open. Control the speed with the speed control for air speed by switching from "Pyt" to "Bosdyx".
	
	As it is a heavy aircraft it needs some special care about propper landing and starting routines :)
	
	Maximal start weight is: 551155 lb = 250.000 kg
      </text>
  
</PropertyList>
