<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>

<PropertyList>

  <title>Antonov An 22</title>
  
  <key>
    <name>d</name>
    <desc>Open/Close left door</desc>
  </key>
  <key>
    <name>D</name>
    <desc>Open/Close right doors</desc>
  </key>
  <key>
    <name>E</name>
    <desc>Open/Close cargo doors</desc>
  </key>
  
  <text>
	Some instruments will show you metric values, some ft.
	
	There is a green panel in the middle console, the right switch makes the lights on.
	
	You have a panel with 5 lamps in the middle, the lower 3 are for trim-neutralisation.
	
	The Key F2 is prepared for reverse, but unfortunatly it is not working (any help to get it working is wellcome).
	
	The Autopilot Helper panel in the top middle console is fully working.You may use some instruments to put in the values -
	- Heading Control: Heading Bug (HDG) and Course of ILS (NAV) are to set in the HSI (Horizontal Situation Indicator),
	- Velocity Control: Speed with Throttle are set in the Speed Indicator, then push IAS
	- Pitch/Attitude Control is working if you get the plane in a climbing or descending position and push the Button VS,
	- Wing leveler is activ when you push the AP button, it is also the AP activating Button,
	- APRP is used for intersepting the Glide Scope,
	- GPS for flying routes from the Route Manager,
	- ALT is holding your attidude
	
	For ILS Landing you may use the little Instrument with the yellow and blue strips, the NAV Indicator, it
	gives you the indication that ILS and/or Glide Scope is intersepted.
	
	Flaps Controll Panel will give you the right level for landing (on the right side) and starting (on the left side),
	if the white strips are in the middle position (1-2 for starting, 2-4 for landing).
	
	Pushback car is now there. Do not use the brakes to stop backwards driving, use the pushback control please.
	
	Trails are now working only above 6000 ft, on ground it is not realistic.
	
	There are 2 Altimeters: one is in meter and mmHG, the other one in ft and inHG,
	 they are connected and you should set them to the ATIS information of the airport befor starting (not working for now).
	 
	The compasses are not cleared of the magnetic variation, it will be done soon. 
      </text>
  
</PropertyList>
